Ismay, Lou; Papers ua902.064
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Student Writings, 1969-1977; Undated; 4; 11.75 cubic ft.
  - Mark Edward, An Opinion of the Fate of Environmental Studies: Past and Future, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Marks, Shari, Community Garden Legislation, 1976 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Marks, Shari, Community Gardening: An Expanding approach to Urban Land Reclamation, 1975 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)
  - Marks, Shari, untitled, 1975 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 14)
  - Marriot, Bob; Molineaux, Ian; Rowett, Hank; The Quality of Environment, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Martel, K., Environmental Education, 1971 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Martel, Kathleen, Recent Developments in Environmental Education, 1970 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Martens, Kay, Cognative Mapping, 1973 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Martens, Kay, A Program of Correct Terms for Cognitive Style Maps, 1973 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Martin, Jonathon, Plastics Recycling for Consumer Re-use and Fuel Alterates, 1975 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Martin, Vaughan, Sterilization, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21)
  - Marzitelli, Thomas, The Adverse Effects of Loud Rock Music, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 22)
  - Mason, Sam, Taps for the Alaskan Environment, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 23)
  - Mastaitis, Vicki, Lake Erie: An Example of Man's Waste, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 24)
  - Mastrangelo, Ed, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 25)
  - Matluck, Eileen The Disposable Marriage, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 26)
  - Matsil, Richard; Kamin, Edward; Drug Education in the Junior High School, 1973 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 27)
  - Matzke, John, A Personal Reflection, 1970 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 28)
  - Maynard, Gregg, The Toxicity of Synthetic Detergents and Soap to Freshwater Fish, 1973 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 29)
  - Mayol, Gilbert, Solar Heating and SUNY at Albany, 1977 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30)
  - McCarville, Patricia, The Right to Counsel for the Poor, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 31)
  - McCrea, Sharon, Blessed are the Merciful, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - McDaniel, Robert, Explorations into Communication, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33)
  - McDermott, John, Alcoholism: The Problem and its Rehabilitation, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 34)
  - McDermott, John, Noise -- The Third Pollution, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 35)
  - McDermott, John, The Relationship Between the Environment and Cardiovascular Disease, 1973 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36)
  - Mcginnis, Carolyn, Architectual Psychology, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 37)
  - Mcintyre, Pam, Midterm, 1976 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - McKay, Lynne, Aspects of Adoption Statutes Application and Fallacies, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - McKinley, Daniel, You Save A Marsh and what do you think happened then?, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40)
  - McMorrow, Patrice, Anne Recovering Indian Lands; The Land Patent Annulment Suit, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 41)
  - McNab, Judy, untitled, 1975 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - McNulty, Ellen, InDefense of the Rape Victim, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 43)
  - Meckler, Rick; Flamn, Scott; untitled, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 44)
  - Meierhoffer, Elise, The Energy Crisis as it affects SUNYA, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 45)
  - Meilunas, Mary Kay, Maternity Leaves: A Survey of Possibilities, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 46)
  - Meloni, Robert, The Beverage Container Problem: Analysis and a Proposed Solution, 1977 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 47)
  - Mercer, Jessie, NY State Legislation, 1971 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 48)
  - Merritt, Harold, The Summer Scene, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 49)
  - Metayer, Gary, Protect Our Environment, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 50)
  - Meteliz, Lew, Internship with the NY State Assembly Scientific Staff, 1975 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 51)
  - Metz, Jeremy, Independent Study, 1977 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 52)
  - Meyer, Laurena, untitled, 1970 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 53)
  - Meyer, Peggy, Solar Energy, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 54)
  - Michaelson, Marlene, The Wilderness Act, 1977 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 55)
  - Miller, Arthur, Staging A "No-Win", Multi Media Agency Proceeding, 1975 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 56)
  - Miller, Laurel; Lieberman, Wendy; Survey for the Conservationist, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 57)
  - Miller, Steven, Diet and Organic Farming, 1976 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 58)
  - Miller, Steven, Tug Hill, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 59)
  - Minck, Kenneth, Diamond Point Road: Erosion Study, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 60)
  - Mintz, Lauri, Nature and Spirituality, 1975 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 61)
  - Mironchuk, Susan, Fuller Road Compost Site, 1973 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 62)
  - Mis, Annette, An Investigation into Proposed Citizen Suit Legislation in NY State during the 1972-1973 Legislative Session (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 63)
  - Mitchell, Joseph, Environmental Pollution of Food Containers and its Effects upon Health and Nutrition, 1973 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 64)
  - Mitchell, Laura, High Rents in the Black Community, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 65)
  - Mogul, David, the Exploitation of the Sea Bed, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 66)
  - Mogul, David, The Museum & Environmental Education, 1976 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 67)
  - Moody, Dick, The Meaning of Impact, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 68)
  - Morris, Bradley, Comprehensive Land Use Planning in Oregon, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 69)
  - Morris, Robert, The Effect of Rat Control on Rats and the Environment, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 70)
  - Moscowitz, Anne; Moscowitz, Gary; Meyer, Jim; untitled, 1970 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 71)
  - Mosoff, Fern; Monk, Patricia; Paulin, Jeff; Chicken Shit: And Other Waste from the Industry, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 72)
  - Mozlin, Stuart; Milfred, Leslie; Dolinsky, Zelig; The Effect of Automobile Produced Soil Compaction and Oil upon Campus trees, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 73)
  - Murphy, Eileen, Final, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 74)
  - Mylatt, John, untitled, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 75)
  - Nagrod, Kathryn, Ocean Disposal of Sewage Sludge: NYC, 1975 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 76)
  - Nangia, D.K., Food Additives, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 77)
  - Needle, Peter, Escherichia Coli and its Effects on the Eutrophication of Harmon Pond, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 78)
  - Needle, Peter, Project on an Electrometer for a Plant, 1976 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 79)
  - Needle, Peter, A Survey of Troy's Freshwater System and Rensselaer County's Sewage Systems, 1976 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 80)
  - Neiwood, Jeb; Paticoff, Gwenn; The Problem of Food Waste at SUNY Albany, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 81)
  - Neufeglise, William Pollution through Negligence -- Santa Barbara, 1973 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 82)
  - Newton, Richard, Thermal Pollution: What is it? Is it a Problem?, 1971 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 83)
  - Newton, Richard, Selections for unit Four of the Second Step Reading Program, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 84)
  - Nichols, Rosemary; Zerbe, Richard; An Annotated Bibliography of Environmental Literature in Legal Periodicals, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 85)
  - Novakowski, Michael, Walk for the Ecology, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 86)
  - Oakes, Nancy, Environmental Information Legislation, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Oakes, Nancy, Lock, 1974 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - O'Brien, Paul, Bicycle Survey, 1974 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Ogden, David, William Preliminary Study for initiating an Aboretum at SUNYA, 1972 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Okrent, Bill, Written Summary, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Oleniczak, Jim, Off Track Betting, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Olsan, Nancy, untitled, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - O'Malley, Christine origin of Marijuana Laws, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - O'Neill, Maureen; Breed, Dudley; Bird Feeding and Journal, 1972 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Osorio, Belinda, Ceremony Among the Sioux and the Dakotas in the 1980s, 1974 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Ouderkirk, David, Additional Use of Open Space in Albany County, 1976 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Ouderkirk, David, Environmental Education, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Ouderkirk, David, Open Space, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)
  - Pace, Robert, and others Student Environmental Association, 1972 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 14)
  - Padula, Stephen, The Santa Barbara Oil Spill, 1975 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Paisley, Joseph, Background Study for Mapping, 1971 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Parnes, Jeffrey, The Ramifications of USA vs. Green, 1972 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Patterson, Barbara, Black Education, 1972 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Pattison, Herbert, Marijuana: Should it be Legal?, 1972 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Pazer, Barbara, Implications of Forrester's World Model, 1971 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Peck, Ronald, Atlantic Cement CO. and the Environment, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21)
  - Pedler, Eleanor, Water Control: Public Interest or Political Play?, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 22)
  - Pepper, Kathy, Wildlife Conservation, 1975 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 23)
  - Pepper, Tim, Planckton: The Mighty Mites, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 24)
  - Perchik, Robyn, Providing Students with a Safer and Healthier Environment, 1977 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 25)
  - Perecman, David; Kramer, Barbara Licensing of Pet Shops, 1975 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 26)
  - Perlee, Bria,n The "Silent" Pollutant: Noise, 1972 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 27)
  - Perlmutter, Daniel, Pollution and the New Treatment Plant on the Cayadutta Creek, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 28)
  - Phillips, Ellen, Negligence and Nursing, 1973 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 29)
  - Plaat, Mark; Treisman, Stephen; Laundry Detergents and The Environment, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30)
  - Platt, Jodi, Salmonella in Animal Products, 1976 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 31)
  - Pollastrino, Karen Predator Pesticides as used in Coyote Control, 1975 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - Polner, Beth, Final, 1977 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33)
  - Polonis, Linda, Aspects of Environmental Education, 1975 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 34)
  - Porte, Eloise, The Eggs that Didn't Hatch, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 35)
  - Powell, Ann, My Learnings at Issac Truax, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36)
  - Powell, Jerome; Cohen, Mark The Controversy of Student Voting, 1972 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 37)
  - Prince, Phil; Malisoff, Keith; Koeppel, Peter; PAN Peroxyacetyl Nitrate and other Photochemical Pollutants, 1974 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - Prince, Phil; Koeppel, Peter; Survival Hike, 1974 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - Project Report, 1970 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40-41)
  - Project Reports, 1973; 1971; 1972; 1976; Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - Project Reports, 1971 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 43)
  - Project Reports, 1972 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 44-45)
  - Project Report, 1973 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 46-47)
  - Project Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 48)
  - Project Reports, 1974 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 49-50)
  - Project Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 51)
  - Project Reports, 1975 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 52-54)
  - Project Reports, 1976 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 55-58)
  - Project Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 59)
  - Project Reports, 1977 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 60)
  - Projector Accident, 1974 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 61)
  - Prolaye, Larry, Gasoline: Today and Tomorrow, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 62)
  - Prusiniski, Diane, The Pine Bush -- A Brief History from Colonial Times to the Present, 1977 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 63)
  - Prusinski, Diane, Summary Report on the Conference of The Future of Education at the Institute on Man and Science in Rensselaerville, NY, 1977 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 64)
  - Puretz, Les; Barber, David, Water Pollution Study in Feura Bush, 1973 (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 65)
  - Quigg, Josep,h Letter to Jimmy Carter, Undated (Box 8 (4-Student Writings), Folder 66)
  - Raiken, Robin; Valentine, Michael; Birth Control Presentation, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Raiken, Robin, Roles of the male and female in our Society, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Ralston, Mark The Grapevine - It's First Year of Growth, 1976 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Randall, Lynn, Thoughts on Todays Education, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Rappaport, Howard, Russ Adult Education program at the Capital District Psychiatric Center, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Rappazzo, Charles, Noise Assessment & Architectural Survey, 1975 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Rappazzo, Chuck, The Effects of Thermal Pollution on the Biology of Freshwater Ecosystems, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Rappazzo, Chuck, Journal, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Ray, Vick, Tails -- You Lose!, 1972 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Redosh, Douglas, A New York State Assembly Interns Report, 1976 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Regan, Richard; Lockrow, Charles; Sewage and an Introduction to the Existing and Proposed Wastewater Facilities of the Capital District Region, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Regan, Richard, untitled, 1976 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Reinertsen, Lee, untitled, 1968 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)
  - Reinertsen, Lee, untitled, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 14)
  - Reisman, Barbara, No Fault Automobile Insurance, 1972 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Reisman, Richard, Reapproachment and State Legislatures, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Renshaw, Edward, Man and His Environment: Part 2, 1970 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Ressler, David; Solomon, Martin, 1971 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Ribak, Charles, Air Pollution and its Effect on the I-88 Corridor, 1971 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Rieben, Gil, Wiretapping -- An Invasion of Privacy?, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Rigterink, Dan, Untitled, 1970 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21)
  - Rimberg, Alan; Lopitz, Stephen; Noise Levels in Albany, 1976 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 22)
  - Rine, Jasper, The Biological Errors Involved in Building the Proposed Blenheim- Breakabeen Pumped Storage Project, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 23)
  - Ringle, Eric; Polansky, Freddy; A Consumer Study of Three Supermarket Chains in the Albany Area, 1977 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 24)
  - Riley, Julian, New Encon Act May have Costly Impact, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 25)
  - Robertson, Edward, Town of Guilderland, 1975 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 26)
  - Robinson, John, Technology and Values: The Wages of Synergy, 1971 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 27)
  - Rogoff, Ira, Tree Planting Slides, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 28)
  - Rohrs, Stephen, Death on the Moon, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 29)
  - Rosenberg, Alex; Berland, Larry; High School Student Survey, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30)
  - Rosenbush, Sharon; Vilardi, Kathy; Field, John; The Causes and remedies of Litter, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 31)
  - Rosenthal, Harvey, untitled, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - Ross, Dan, untitled, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33)
  - Ross, Jean; Chertok, Fern; Sensory Awareness Teachers Manual (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 34)
  - Roth, Bruce Causes of truck Noise and its Effect on Drivers and the Environment, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 35)
  - Rourke, Daniel, New York State Environmental Conservation Commission and Interim Wetlands Report, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36)
  - Rourke, Daniel, Open Space and Natural Resource Inventory for the Town of Coeymans, New York, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 37)
  - Rourke, Daniel, Open Space Inventory of Wetlands, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - Rubin, Stuart Survival, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - Rudolf, Kenneth Photographic Essay on Mass Production, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40)
  - Rugh, Ann; Uttley, Louis Sex Discrimination in the Finacial World, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 41)
  - Russel, Royce, The Rationale Behind Determining the Legal Stature of an Individual by Chronological Age, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - Russo, Seth Lake Eerie Offshore Natural Gas Development, 1977 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 43)
  - Sachs, Bruce, Tent and Camping Equipment Safety, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 44)
  - Saeger, Mark, Kirlian Photography Project, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 45)
  - Salamon, David, Historical Site Survey:Thurlow Terrace, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 46)
  - Salamon, David, Paper Recycling Program, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 47)
  - Sapurstein, Bert, Miscegenation, 1972 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 48)
  - Sass, Heidi, Law and the Professional Baseball Player, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 49)
  - Savoni, Joseph, Contstuction Material Left in the Woods in Back of SUNYA's Infirmary, 1972 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 50)
  - Schaber, Michael, Legal Regulation of Pesticides, 1975 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 51)
  - Schanche, Don, A Proposed Bridge Across Long Island Sound, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 52)
  - Scharf, Irene, The Use of Vacant Lots in Albany For Gardening, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 53)
  - Schatz, Don, Administrative Behavior, 1975 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 54)
  - Scheinfeld, Hedy; Allen, Barbara The Effects of Granola, Wonder Bread and Mouse Chow on Laboratory Mice, 1976 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 55)
  - Schere, Michael, Noise Pollution, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 56)
  - Schlagel, Amy, Attitudes and Opinions of Hisotric Preservation: Questionnaire and Analysis, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 57)
  - Schmilowitz, Abraham, Trends in Early Sherman Law, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 58)
  - Schneier, Carol, On Modeling Systems and Managing, 1971 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 59)
  - Schneier, Joan, SUNYA Impact Statement Water, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 60)
  - Schnepper, Michael, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 61)
  - Schou, Bertil, Mass Transportation as an Alternative to the the Automobile and the Problems facing it, 1975 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 62)
  - Schubert, Jaik, Paper & Paper Recycling, 1971 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 63)
  - Schulberg, Francine, Thermal Pollution, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 64)
  - Schut, Ardys, untitled, 1970 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 65)
  - Schwartz, Steven, Journal, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 66)
  - Schwedfeger, Paul, The Okwari Park Controversy, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 67)
  - Schwedfeger, Paul, The Outer Banks of North Carolina: unchanged, yet ever changing, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 68)
  - Scola, Pamela, Final Paper, 1975 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 69)
  - Scull, Jack, A Review of the Downtown Recycling Project, 1972 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 70)
  - Segerstrom, Dick, Argument Against Abortion, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 71)
  - Seidman, Robert, A Critical Analysis of the use of Solar Energy and its Relation to the Alumni House, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 72)
  - Selwyn, Gary, Chemical Analysis of Phenols, 1973 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 73)
  - Selwyn, Gary, A Chemical and Ecological Study of the Campus Lake, 1972 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 74)
  - Selwyn, Gary, An Undergraduate Research Study of chemical Pollution in the Campus Pond, 1972 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 75)
  - Sengenberger, John Bottle Bill Legislation, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 76)
  - Sepa, Carol Ann, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 77)
  - Serbalik, June, Saratoga Lake, 1976 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 78)
  - Severenson, Michael; Bass, Ron Determination of Leadand other Pollutants of the 6 Mile Waterways, Albany, NY, 1975 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 79)
  - Severance, Michael, Inadvertent Environmental modification of Urban Industrial Areas, 1974 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 80)
  - Sgroi, Robert, Nuclear Energy and You, 1975 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 81)
  - Shaffer, Steve, Abortion in New York, 1972 (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 82)
  - Shahanian, Ani; Borgman, Amy; Paper Recycling, Undated (Box 9 (4-Student Writings), Folder 83)
  - Sharfstein, Howard, Standing & environmental Litigation, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Sheer, John; Decesare, Doug Aid to Parochial Schools as Seen by the Supreme Court, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Sheldon, Robin, From Egg Viability in Selected Waters of the Hudson River and its Tributaries, 1976 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Shemella, Andrew, The Student Lobby, 1976 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Sherman, David Survey; Heating Quality at State University of New York at Albany, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Sherman, Julie, untitled, 1977 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Sherman, Mitchell, The Atlantic Salmon, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Sherman, Paul, Constitutional Impediments to Population Control, 1972 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Sherman, Randolph, The Pinebush Project: Recapitulation, 1973 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Shulgin, Tanya untitled, 1973 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Shustak, Lenore; Cohen, Jeremy; Hering, Thomas; The odds are Against us: Cars today, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Sianusso, Pete, Auto Engines: What are our Alternatives, Undated (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Simins, Maryann, Buckminster Fuller World Game Theory, 1971 (Box 10 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)